National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap298
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, 1976-2001, Undated; 6; 1.95 cubic ft.
  - Adjoa Aiyetoro, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Alabamians Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Alan and Lindsay, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Autographed Portraits, Illegible, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 45)
  - Hugo Bedau, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 46)
  - Book Signing: Hele Prejean, William Styron, Rose Styron, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 47)
  - Susan Boster, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 48)
  - Justice Brennan, Sister Helen Prejean, Susan Sarender, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 49)
  - Bruderhof Community, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 50)
  - Dick Burr and Leigh Dingerson, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 51)
  - Jeb Bash, Signed portrait, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 52)
  - C. Byers, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 53)
  - Johnny Cochran and Steve Hawkins, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 54)
  - Steve Dean, Governor George Ryan, Mike Farrell, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 55)
  - Death Penalty in the Arts Plenany, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 56)
  - Delegation at European Parliament, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 57)
  - Leigh Dengesen, Bob Gross, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 58)
  - Awi Detruico, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 59)
  - Micki Dickoff, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 60)
  - Leigh Dingeraon, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 61)
  - Totaka Eaddy and Suemyra Shah, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 62)
  - Steve Earie, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 63)
  - David Elliot, Communications Director, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 64)
  - Film Negatives, Undated (Box 2 (6-Photographs), Folder 65)
  - Film Negatives, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - K. Fox, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Stephanie Gibson, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Danny Glove, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Rick Halperin, Marietta Yaeger, Bill Pelke, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Steve Hawkins, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Steve Hawkins and Rev. Jessie Jackson, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Steve Hawkins and Governor Ryan, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Steve Hawkins and Melody Smith, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Maria Hines, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Houston, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Individuals Speaking, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Joe Ingle, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Rev. Jessie Jackson, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Sunny Jacobs, Paula E., Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Jay Jacobson, Rachel Key, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Jeu, Tim Spann, Nick, Carol Byers, John Mosher, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Pope John Paul ll, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - "Jotaka's Picture", Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Ken-e, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Coretta Scott King, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Jessica Landry-Baters, Youth Activist Awardee, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Laura and Jessica, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Brenda Lewis, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Brenda Lewis and Frank Ballance, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Los Angeles White Supremacist, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Rev. Joe Loweny, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Sam Moretta, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Migel Martinez (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Terry Mooney (OK) - Juvenile, 16 yr, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - National Coalition members, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Negatives with CD, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Negatives with CD, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Helen Pajama, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Paula E., Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Bill Pelke, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Pittsburgh, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Photograph of man during trial, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 3 (6-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 4 (6-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Photographs used for publications, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Phyllis Patraut, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Postcard to Faye Chappell, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Press Interview on night of Joseph O' Dell's execution in Virginia, 1997 (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, Lisa Radalet, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Sister Helen Prejean, Bryan Stevens, Mike Fawell, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Rachel, Bill and Judy, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - K+H Robinson, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - D. Routerice, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Sally P, Carol D, Sally Peck, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Susan Sarandon, Tim Robbins, Sister Helen Prejean and Sister Theresa Bangert, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Sam Sheppard, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - St. Louis, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - "Symboliz", Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Desmond Tutu, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Radio Vaticana - 35 millimeter slide, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Sue Vanghu and Steve Hawkins, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Christie Webb, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Bud Welch, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Charlie Wilton, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - X-Mas March, Rome, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Marietta Yaeger, Leno Rose Andir, Undated (Box 5 (6-Photographs), Folder 27)
- Audio, 1981-2005, Undated; 7; 0.35 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by the creator's last name or title of material.
  Recorded cassette tapes and one compact disc with recordings of NCADP annual conferences, radio shows, and executions.
  - Alive Todaym Death Row Callins, USA - A.J. Bannister to Steven Hawkins, 1997 July 11 (Cassette 1)
  - Jim Beardon, R. A. H., 1992 (Cassette 2)
  - Capital Punishment: A Thirst for Blood or Justice, Attorney Rod Jones; Radio Segments - "Justice Blinded" Series KZYX/KMUD Public Radio, Undated (Cassette 3)
  - Coalition for the Death Penalty, 1981 October 4 (Cassette 4)
  - Judy C. Cumbee "Bringin' Abolition Day!" [commercial music], Undated (Cassette 5)
  - Death Penalty Features KPBX Spokane 2-24, 25, 26-87, Undated (Cassette 6)
  - Death Penalty - Texas "Primetime" ch. 12 Phoenix Arizona, 9:45 pm, 1997 February 26 (Cassette 7)
  - L. C. Dorsey, Saturday Afternoon, Undated (Cassette 8)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Atlanta, NCADP Program Parts 1, 2, 1990 May 18 (Cassette 9)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church Atlanta, NCADP Program Parts 3, 4, 1990 May 18 (Cassette 10)
  - Execution - Randy Greenawalt, 1997 January 23 (Cassette 11)
  - Execution - Jimmie Wayne Jeffers, Arizona State Prison, 1995 September 13 (Cassette 12)
  - From Death Row: This is Mumia Abu-Jamal, Undated (Cassette 13)
  - Dr. Jim Grigson, Psychiatrist Texas Death Row, Undated (Cassette 14)
  - Ben Jealous, 30 minute interview with Joseph Payne on death row in Virginia and his lawyer Paul Khoury, 1996 October 28 (Cassette 15)
  - John and Ken Show, 3-4 pm KFI AM 640/KOST 103 FM, 1995 December 5 (Cassette 16)
  - National Public Radio: "All Things Considered" on medical participation report (breach of trust), 1994 April 3 (Cassette 17)
  - National Public Radio: William Brennan, Supreme Court Justice, 1987 (Cassette 18)
  - National Public Radio: Loyal Garner Jr. case, 1988 August 10 (Cassette 19)
  - National Public Radio: Diane Rhems, Mikel Gilmore new book, Shot in the Heart, 1994 May 25 (Cassette 20)
  - National Public Radio: The Diane Rhems Show, The Death Penalty, 2005 December 5 (Cassette 21)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 2, 1981 September 26-27 (Cassette 22)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 3, 1981 September 26-27 (Cassette 23)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 4, 1981 September 26-27 (Cassette 24)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 5, 1981 September 26-27 (Cassette 25)
  - NCADP National Conference 1981 Tape 6, 1981 September 26-27 (Cassette 26)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Rodney Young & Robert R. Bryan: Race, Politics and Death in the 90s, 1990 November 9 (Cassette 27)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Rodney Young & Robert R. Bryan: Race, Politics and Death in the 90s, 1990 November 9 (Cassette 28)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Rodney Young & Robert R. Bryan: Race, Politics and Death in the 90s, 1990 November 9 (Cassette 29)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Changing the Focus: A Realistic Look at Crime and Offenders, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 30)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Changing the Focus: A Realistic Look at Crime and Offenders, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 31)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Changing the Focus: A Realistic Look at Crime and Offenders, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 32)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Preventing Reinstatement: Jonathon Gradess, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 33)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Preventing Reinstatement: Jonathon Gradess, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 34)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Preventing Reinstatement: Jonathon Gradess, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 35)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Taking Action: The Role of Civil Disobedience for Social Change, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 36)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Taking Action: The Role of Civil Disobedience for Social Change, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 37)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Working With Victims' Families: Adele Shank, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 38)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Working With Victims' Families: Adele Shank, 1990 November 10 (Cassette 39)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Dr. Joseph Lowery, Robert R. Bryan, 1990 November 11 (Cassette 40)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Dr. Joseph Lowery, Robert R. Bryan, 1990 November 11 (Cassette 41)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Rev. Dr. Joseph Lowery, Robert R. Bryan Closing Address, 1990 November 11 (Cassette 42)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Real Victims, Real Responses, 1990 November 11 (Cassette 43)
  - NCADP National Conference 1990 - Real Victims, Real Responses, 1990 November 11 (Cassette 44)
  - New Voices - 247, Public Interest Video Network, 1990 December 10 (Cassette 45)
  - News Broadcast "Death Penalty" 8:17 PM, 1997 February 26 (Cassette 46)
  - Prison the Last Option, Background Briefing - Radio National Australia, 1992 March (Cassette 47)
  - Geoffrey Robertson, QC. Death Penalty, Sydney, 1994 February (Cassette 48)
  - The Rope, the Chair, the Needle MD SDV TM, 1998 February 3 (Cassette 49)
  - Jane Stroessner, "Never Say Die", Undated (Cassette 50)
  - Darby J. Tillis, "Death to Life" [commercial music], 2002 (Cd 1)
  - Lem Davis Tubble, Jr., interview from Mecklemberg prison, 1996 November 23 (Cassette 51)
  - Alton Waye, 10 PM, 1989 August 30 (Cassette 52)
  - Howard Zinn: Stop the Death Penalty, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA, 1996 March 11 (Cassette 53)
- Video, 1985-2005; 8; 5.40 cubic ft.
  Recorded VHS and DVD video of television programs, films, and other programs relating to capital punishment in the United States. Many of the items featured members of the NCADP, particularly Steven Hawkins, the former Executive Director
  - 12 Minutes, a Raymond A. Thomas Film, 2001 (Vhs 1)
  - 14 Days in May (execution of Edward Earl Johnson, Undated (Vhs 2)
  - 48 Hours: "Willie Otey" Hanging of Wesley Allen Dodd in Washington State, 1993 (Vhs 3)
  - 48 Hours: Juveniles and the Death Penalty, Undated (Vhs 4)
  - 60 Minutes: Inmate 777, 1997 December 7 (Vhs 5)
  - About the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty in German, 1999 (Vhs 6)
  - ACLE "Juvenile Justice: Unplugged" a field exploration by and for students, 1997 (Vhs 7)
  - Alabama Coalition Speakers Bureau Training - Dennis Balskem Esq. speaks for the Alabama Coalition, 1986 (Vhs 8)
  - America's Black Forum Show #PR1-99/00-13R "Capital Punishment Debate", 1999 November 3; 2000 June 18 (Vhs 9)
  - America's Black Forum Show #PR1-99/00-13R "Capital Punishment Debate", 1999 November 3; 2000 June 18 (Vhs 10)
  - America's Black Forum Show #PR1-99/00-13R "Capital Punishment Debate" Race Issues, 1999 November 3; 2000 June 18 (Vhs 11)
  - American Bar Association - Executing Injustice: ABA Call for a Moratorium on Executions, Undated (Vhs 12)
  - American Forum, Hurricane Advisory: Popular Culture and Capital Punishment, Undated (Vhs 13)
  - Amnesty Death Penalty, Undated (Vhs 14)
  - Amnesty International USA "Campaign Against the Death Penalty", Undated (Vhs 15)
  - Amnesty International USA "The Next Step", Undated (Vhs 16)
  - Amnesty International USA "The Next Step", Undated (Vhs 17)
  - Balancing Justice and Mercy: a group of law officials and others discussing the criminal justice system and capital punishment, Undated (Vhs 18)
  - Balancing the Scale: Robert Gilliand, 1989 March 15 (Vhs 19)
  - Balancing the Scales - The Texas Moratorium Network, Undated (Dvd 1)
  - Odell Barnes Defense, 2000 January 15 (Dvd 2)
  - Odell Barnes Defense, 2000 January 15 (Vhs 20)
  - BET - talk with Tavis Smiley: Steven Hawkins along with Busisiwe Chabeil and Chokwe Lumumba, discuss the case of Azi Kambule, Undated (Vhs 21)
  - BET - talk: Steve Hawkins, Executive Director of NCADP, interviews with Tavis Smiley, 1997 (Vhs 22)
  - The Benefits of Representing Capital Defendants Developing Mitigation Claims: Bryan Stevenson discusses the benefits of representing capital defendants. Many Welch discusses how to develop mitigation claims, 1993 June 8 (Vhs 23)
  - "Better Off Dead": Lifetime movie dealing with murder and the death penalty, 1992 December 11 (Vhs 24)
  - William Brennan Project: Interviews & News Conference & Program, raw footage, Undated (Vhs 25)
  - Walter Brooks Show: Steve Hawkins interviews with Walter Brooks to discuss his life as an attorney, 1996 May 3 (Vhs 26)
  - Bush's Deadly Ambition, produced & directed by Micki Dickoff and Tim Tale, Correspondent: David Smith - Channel 4/London, 2000 (Vhs 27)
  - CBS News "Before Your Eyes/One Last Chance" 92:00, 1996 July 23 (Vhs 28)
  - CBS Program - William Andrews questions the racial inequalities that surround the death penalty in the US, Undated (Vhs 29)
  - Campaign Against the Death Penalty: Amnesty International's campaign to end the death penalty 29:30, Undated (Vhs 30)
  - Campaign Against the Death Penalty: Footage from Amnesty International's campaign to end the death penalty 29:30, Undated (Vhs 31)
  - Children's Crusade to Death Row - Plough Publishing, 1997 August 18-20 (Vhs 32)
  - Client: Steven Hawkins, Topic: Morning News - Death Penalty / Delaware, 1996 November 22 (Vhs 33)
  - Cochran and Grace "Death Penalty": Steven Hawkins, Executive Director of NCADP, as well as others discuss capital punishment in America, 1997 January 21 (Vhs 34)
  - Court-TV - A close look at the case of Lloyd Schulp, 1995 June 21 (Vhs 35)
  - Court-TV "Chance & Powell: Back in the World", Undated (Vhs 36)
  - Court-TV On Appeal Show #32, Jones v. Butterworth, 1997 December 29 (Vhs 37)
  - CRLS - Defining the Future [marked "not playing"], Undated (Vhs 38)
  - Crossfire Sunday: Steven Hawkins joins a distinguished panel to debate the death penalty, 1997 June 8 (Vhs 39)
  - Governor [Mario] Cuomo Death Penalty Speech at CSR, 1989 March 13 (Vhs 40)
  - Current Issues - Capital Punishment: Leigh Dingerson, Richard Stamp, and students discuss and debate the death penalty, 1992 May 2 (Vhs 41)
  - Willie Darden - 20/20: the case of Willie Darden, 1988 January (Vhs 42)
  - De Press Conference, Undated (Vhs 43)
  - Debate on the Death Penalty: Both opponents and experts debate the moral and constitutional factors of the death penalty in the United States, 1988 October 4 (Vhs 44)
  - Deadline: a film by Katy Chevigny and Kirsten Johnson [commercial DVD release], 2004 (Dvd 3)
  - Deadline - Sundance Version, 2004 (Vhs 45)
  - Deadline - Texted Letterbox, 2004 (Vhs 46)
  - Death Penalty Advocates, directed by Jesse Limbaugh, Undated (Vhs 47)
  - The Death Penalty in Alaska? Never Again: Alaskans explain why the death penalty was abolished in their state, Undated (Vhs 48)
  - The Death Penalty: Albany Law School, 1991 April 5 (Vhs 49)
  - The Death Penalty: Albany Law School, 1991 April 5 (Vhs 50)
  - The Death Penalty: Albany Law School, 1991 April 6 (Vhs 51)
  - The Death Penalty: Albany Law School, 1991 April 6 (Vhs 52)
  - "The Death Penalty: Justice or Revenge?" - WEDU Tampa, Tom Mills, Producer, 1990 July 20 (Vhs 53)
  - Death Penalty Rally - Albany, NY Rough Cuts Camera #1, 1989 May 23 (Vhs 54)
  - Death Penalty - University of Glasgow Media Services, Undated (Vhs 55)
  - Death Row Friends - 20/20, 2000 August 18 (Vhs 56)
  - Delaware Tonight, 2003 June 5 (Vhs 57)
  - Francis Dunnery - Live in New York City: An excerpt from Francis Dunnery's current album, Undated (Vhs 58)
  - The Empty Chair - Four Stories: Murder Victims' Families Confront Loss & Punishment, 2003 (Vhs 59)
  - The Execution of Raymond Graham - ABC TV Movie, Undated (Vhs 60)
  - The Execution of Raymond Graham: A made for TV movie that spans the last hour of an inmate who is executed by lethal injection, Undated (Vhs 61)
  - Execution of David Lawson - Donahue Special Report, Undated (Vhs 62)
  - Executions: a first hand look at executions past and present all over the world, 1995 (Vhs 63)
  - Eye for an Eye?: This film examines the social injustices of the death penalty in America and in Texas, 1988 August 1 (Vhs 64)
  - Barry Fairchild - 20/20 News: Story of the Barry Fairchild Case. Strong accusations of police misconduct and how that can lead to a wrongful conviction, 1991 March 29 (Vhs 65)
  - Finding a Way: New Initiatives in Justice for Children, 1997 (Vhs 66)
  - Final Judgment: A documentary about the death penalty, Undated (Vhs 67)
  - Firing Line Debate - PBS: Death penalty experts debate this issue, Undated (Vhs 68)
  - First Tuesday Death Row - A One Women Band: The Story of Marie Dean, a abolitionist who works alone to find representation for death row inmates in Virginia, 1986 (Vhs 69)
  - First Tuesday Death Row - A One Women Band: The Story of Marie Dean, a abolitionist who works alone to find representation for death row inmates in Virginia, 1986 (Vhs 70)
  - Florida Crossroads "Female Prison Rates": Cindy Smith of FPTV visits Florida's Death row to interview Andrea Hicks Jackson, one of the five women on death row in Florida, Undated (Vhs 71)
  - Fox News - Shareef Cousin case, WVUE, 1999 January 8-9 (Vhs 72)
  - Fox News: Features Krista Pike, the youngest person on death row, Undated (Vhs 73)
  - Fox News: Steven Hawkins is interviewed about the Timothy McVeigh Trial, 1997 (Vhs 74)
  - Fox News: Steven Hawkins and former US Attorney Joseph Digenova discuss the imposition of the death penalty of juveniles involved in a gang related shooting in SE, Washington, D.C., Undated (Vhs 75)
  - John Wayne Gacy Execution - Media Coverage, 1994 May (Vhs 76)
  - John Wayne Gacy Execution - Media Coverage, 1994 May (Vhs 77)
  - John Sterling Gardner, Jr.: A Case Study of how to recognize child abuse and neglect and intervene Effectively: This discusses how recognition of child abuse effective intervention could have changed John's story as he now sits on death row, Undated (Vhs 78)
  - Juan Raul Garza: Memorandum in Support of Petition for Clemency, Undated (Vhs 79)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #1 Planning for Fundraising, Kim Klein, Trainer 43:10, Undated (Vhs 80)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #2 The Role of the Board, Kim Klein, Trainer 40:50, Undated (Vhs 81)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #3 Raising Money by Mail, Kim Klein, Trainer 51:46, Undated (Vhs 82)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #4 Asking for Money and Prospect Identification, Kim Klein, Trainer 45:28, Undated (Vhs 83)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #5 Major Gift Solicitation, Kim Klein, Trainer 39:15, Undated (Vhs 84)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #6 Special Events, Kim Klein, Trainer 23:00, Undated (Vhs 85)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #1 Planning for Fundraising, Kim Klein, Trainer 43:10, Undated (Vhs 86)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #2 The Role of the Board, Kim Klein, Trainer 40:50, Undated (Vhs 87)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #3 Raising Money by Mail, Kim Klein, Trainer 51:46, Undated (Vhs 88)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #4 Asking for Money and Prospect Identification, Kim Klein, Trainer 45:28, Undated (Vhs 89)
  - Grassroots Fundraising Videotapes - Tape #6 Special Events, Kim Klein, Trainer 23:00, Undated (Vhs 90)
  - Growth Films [unlabeled VHS], Undated (Vhs 91)
  - HBO presents Clomic Stop Space Traders [?], Undated (Vhs 92)
  - Steve Hawkins, Undated (Vhs 93)
  - Steve Hawkins on Court-TV, Undated (Vhs 94)
  - Steve Hawkins on Fox News about Timothy McVeigh, Undated (Vhs 95)
  - Steve Hawkins Interviews 43:30, 1996 April 3 (Vhs 96)
  - Interview with Mike Farrell: ABC interviews Mike Farrell on why he is opposed to the death penalty and his views toward the Mumia Abu Jamal case, 1994 April (Vhs 97)
  - Interview with Joyce Mokhesi: Mokhesi speaks about the case of the Sharpeville Six, Undated (Vhs 98)
  - Jessie Jackson "The Lethal Law": Former death row inmate Paula Cooper and four distinguished panelists debate the death penalty issue and examine its moral status, 1991 March 11 (Vhs 99)
  - Journey of Hope: This tape gives an in-depth view of what JOH is all about, 1993 (Vhs 100)
  - Journey of Hope: Not in My Name, 1995 (Vhs 101)
  - Journey of Hope - Not in Our Names: A documentary of the Journey of Hope which travels across the country proclaiming the negative aspects of the death penalty in America, 1995 (Vhs 102)
  - Justice on Trial: the Case of Gary Graham, 1993 (Vhs 103)
  - Justice on Trial: the Case of Gary Graham - Addendum 7 Years Later, 1999 (Vhs 104)